thank you kind sir can I have five more
mouth sauces I really love the stuff hey
Donovan yo guy over here talking about
hero five mile sauces five five ounces
this is always you three piece wait no
any happening today
no yeah I'm like a loyal customer you
think yes everybody your loyal customer
is Harold's look around always
thank you young man
welcome can I please have a couple of
extra mile sauces yeah ma'am you can
have as many as you want get get us a
mouth I'll just grab it here for you
could have automail sauce with me thank
you how does she get extra mouth sauce
you just made a whole speech about mouth
off
she a black one my life is hard enough
all right you know what this doesn't
seem fair okay Oh fair all right here's
fair right you get old and new mouths
all stains on your clothes how about you
just take that chicken
rub it on your outfit if you want
mouth sauce just get it from your mama
cuz she a ho wait how does my mother
being a prostitute get me in the
possession of more maltose okay that is
a great follow up question you are a
very intelligent young man
um your mama said dig for Mouse how's
your week
you